<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<games>
    <game gameCode="1">
        <title>Tekken 7</title>
        <developer>BANDAI NAMCO Studios Inc.</developer>
        <publisher>BANDAI NAMCO Entertainment</publisher>
        <genre>Fighting</genre>
        <price>800</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2017-06-02</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
        Discover the epic conclusion of the long-time clan warfare between members of the Mishima family. Powered by Unreal Engine 4, the legendary fighting game franchise fights back with stunning story-driven cinematic battles and intense duels that can be enjoyed with friends and rivals.
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/tekken7.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="2">
        <title>Risk of Rain 2</title>
        <developer>Hopoo Games</developer>
        <publisher>Gearbox Publishing</publisher>
        <genre>Indie</genre>
        <price>500</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2020-08-11</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
        Escape a chaotic alien planet by fighting through hordes of frenzied monsters – with your friends, or on your own. Combine loot in surprising ways and master each character until you become the havoc you feared upon your first crash landing.
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/ror2.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="3">
        <title>Grand Theft Auto V</title>
        <developer>Rockstar North</developer>
        <publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <price>1200</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2015-04-14</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
        Grand Theft Auto V for PC offers players the option to explore the award-winning world of Los Santos and Blaine County in resolutions of up to 4k and beyond, as well as the chance to experience the game running at 60 frames per second.
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/gtaV.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="4">
        <title>Monster Hunter World</title>
        <developer>CAPCOM Co., Ltd.</developer>
        <publisher>CAPCOM Co., Ltd.</publisher>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <price>1000</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2018-08-10</dateOfRelease>
        <description>Welcome to a new world! In Monster Hunter: World, the latest installment in the series, you can enjoy the ultimate hunting experience, using everything at your disposal to hunt monsters in a new world teeming with surprises and excitement.</description>
        <imagePath>images/mhw.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="5">
        <title>Dead by Daylight</title>
        <developer>Behaviour Interactive Inc.</developer>
        <publisher>Behaviour Interactive Inc.</publisher>
        <genre>Thriller</genre>
        <price>800</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2016-06-14</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
        Dead by Daylight is a multiplayer (4vs1) horror game where one player takes on the role of the savage Killer, and the other four players play as Survivors, trying to escape the Killer and avoid being caught and killed.
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/deadByDaylight.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="6">
        <title>Stardew Valley</title>
        <developer>ConcernedApe</developer>
        <publisher>ConcernedApe</publisher>
        <genre>Simulation</genre>
        <price>400</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2016-02-27</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
        You have inherited your grandfathers old farm plot in Stardew Valley. Armed with hand-me-down tools and a few coins, you set out to begin your new life. Can you learn to live off the land and turn these overgrown fields into a thriving home?
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/stardewValley.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="7">
        <title>Terraria</title>
        <developer>Re-Logic</developer>
        <publisher>Re-Logic</publisher>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <price>400</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2011-05-17</dateOfRelease>
        <description>Dig, fight, explore and build. Nothing is impossible in this action-packed adventure game.</description>
        <imagePath>images/terraria.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="8">
        <title>Tom Clancy Rainbow Six Siege</title>
        <developer>Ubisoft Montreal</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <price>400</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2011-05-17</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
         Tom Clancy Rainbow Six Siege is the latest installment of the acclaimed first-person shooter franchise developed by the renowned Ubisoft Montreal studio.
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/rainbowSixSiege.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="9">
        <title>Rust</title>
        <developer>Facepunch Studios</developer>
        <publisher>Facepunch Studios</publisher>
        <genre>Survival</genre>
        <price>1500</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2018-02-09</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
        The only aim in Rust is to survive. Everything wants you to die - the island’s wildlife and other inhabitants, the environment, other survivors. Do whatever it takes to last another night.
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/rust.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="10">
        <title>Red Dead Redemption 2</title>
        <developer>Rockstar Games</developer>
        <publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <price>2000</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2019-12-06</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
        Winner of over 175 Game of the Year Awards and recipient of over 250 perfect scores, RDR2 is the epic tale of outlaw Arthur Morgan and the infamous Van der Linde gang, on the run across America at the dawn of the modern age. Also includes access to the shared living world of Red Dead Online.
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/redDeadRedemption2.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="11">
        <title>Hades</title>
        <developer>Supergiant Games</developer>
        <publisher>Supergiant Games</publisher>
        <genre>Indie</genre>
        <price>600</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2019-12-11</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
        Defy the god of the dead as you hack and slash out of the Underworld in this rogue-like dungeon crawler from the creators of Bastion, Transistor, and Pyre.
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/hades.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
    <game gameCode="12">
        <title>Fall Guys</title>
        <developer>Mediatonic</developer>
        <publisher>Mediatonic</publisher>
        <genre>Casual</genre>
        <price>300</price>
        <dateOfRelease>2020-08-04</dateOfRelease>
        <description>
        Fall Guys is a massively multiplayer party game with up to 60 players online in a free-for-all struggle through round after round of escalating chaos until one victor remains.
        </description>
        <imagePath>images/fallGuys.jpg</imagePath>
    </game>
</games>